unwrapindia.com 2013-05-31

# None

* Use of the Site and the Service is further governed by Adjetter Media Network's Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into this Agreement by reference. Adjetter Media Network Private Limited is the operator and licensee of [www.unwrapindia.com](http://www.unwrapindia.com/). We ensure the protection and security of your personal information.

Personal Information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person, to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, IP address, name, physical address, email address, phone number, cell phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, identification number and credit card information and other information such as gender, occupation and other demographic information.

#### With whom does UWI share my personally identifiable information?

We don't sell your name or other personally identifiable information to third parties. We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services.

We may use your IP address and share it with third parties to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage the Site and the Service, and to enhance the Site and the Service based on usage pattern data.

#### How does UWI use cookies, tags, and similar technologies?

We use cookies, tags and similar technologies to recognize your preferences and effectively and efficiently administer the Site. We use the information we collect to enhance your visit to the Site and provide you with information tailored to your interests.

You may elect to refuse cookies, however doing so may affect your use of some portions of the Services and our partners services.

#### Does the Site contain links to other websites?

unwrapindia.com may contain links to other sites not owned by us that may have different privacy practices from ours. We aren't responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy doesn't apply to information collected by those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you. When you leave our Site or Service via a link to interact with a site not governed by our Privacy Policy, a new browser window will open.

#### How is my personally identifiable information protected?

To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or improper use of your information, and to maintain data accuracy, we've established reasonable physical, electronic and managerial safeguards to protect the information we collect. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information, we can't be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

#### How should I contact UWI about my personally identifiable information?

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use or disclosure of your personally identifiable information, please write to us at:

**Adjetter Media Network Pvt Ltd**  
2nd Floor, Tech Park   
PESIT Campus, 100 Ft Ring Road,  
BanaShankari 3rd Stage,   
Bangalore - 560085, India.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

If the privacy policy is changed, UWI will post changes so that you are aware of those changes. If UWI makes material changes to this policy you will be notified by email, or other places UWI deems appropriate.UWI reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.
